翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）
So the next step we're going to do--
下一步我们要做的是
and this is going to seem like an almost seemingly equally pointless exercise--
这看起来几乎同样毫无意义
is we're going to create another class which I'll call SLList
我们要创建另一个类 SLList
with two L's.
有两个 L
And this class is going to represent--
这个类将代表...
an SLList is a list of integers which hides the terrible truth of the nakedness within.
SLList 是一个整型 List，它隐藏了内部裸露的可怕真相
And how this list is going to work is, well we already have a perfectly good int list class.
这个 List 的工作原理是，我们已经有了一个非常好的 IntList 类
I mean it's called IntNode now.
现在叫 IntNode
So I'm going to make a variable an SLList called public--
我要命名一个变量叫...
sorry.
抱歉
I'm going to declare a variable on SLList.
我要在 SLList 上声明一个变量
So it will be public IntNode first.
public IntNode first
And then I'll have a constructor for SLList, public SLList Int x.
然后有一个构造函数，public SLList(int x)
First equals new IntNode, x null.
first = new IntNode(x, null)
And at that point, once I've written this class,
这时我写完这个类后
I can do something like SLList L equals new SLList list 10.
可以这样做，比如 SLList L = new SLList(10)
And what this code does is it creates a list of one integer, namely 10.
这段代码创建了包含一个整型的 List，值为10
So what's good about this?
这有什么优点呢？
Why have we done this seemingly pointless exercise in bureaucracy?
为什么要做这种看似毫无意义的工作呢？
Well, this is a little bit of a clue.
这是一个小提示
If you think about how I,
想一想
some programmer, have created a list, I did not have to actually specify null.
程序员创建 List 时无需指定 null
An SLList does not have that property.
SLList 没有这个属性
You're just given an x And that's it.
提供一个 x 就行了
So if we compare the old way of doing things,
跟之前比较一下
IntList to IntNodes, we can look at the declaration of a new naked recursive list-- it looks something like this--
IntList 到 IntNode，裸露 List 的声明是这样
and a new hiding the nakedness from the world list.
new 一个隐藏裸露的 List 是这样
So IntNode, in this case we see that we have to specify the address manually.
IntNode 必须手动指定地址
Now that's also a pretty minor improvement.
这是一个很小的进步
But it gives us a sense of where we're going with this.
但为我们找到了思路
The programmer who's using an SLList,
使用 SLList 的程序员
they need not think about references.
不需要考虑引用
They don't have to specify the null.
不必指定 null
And that same property is going to recur as we build up our other methods.
当我们建立其他方法时，同样的性质也会重复出现
There will be no need to even be thinking about any of this naked recursion.
甚至不需要考虑任何裸露在外的递归
翻译：@隐秀_（seriouszyx）